<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="skip_text">skip</string>
    <string name="welcome_text">Welcome to</string>
    <string name="vizo">Vizo</string>
    <string name="intro_text">Get the latest and most relevant news\n stories without fumbling through\n newspapers and aggregators.</string>

    <!-- String Resources for Category Names -->
    <string name="cat_business">Business</string>
    <string name="cat_politics">Politics</string>
    <string name="cat_sports">Sports</string>
    <string name="cat_art_culture">Arts &amp; Culture</string>
    <string name="cat_technology">Technology</string>
    <string name="cat_top_news">Top News</string>
    <string name="cat_us">U.S.</string>
    <string name="cat_world">World</string>
    <string name="cat_celebrities">Celebrity</string>
    <string name="cat_vizou">Vizo U</string>
    <string name="cat_science">Science</string>

    <!-- String Resource for Onboarding -->
    <string name="your_world_at_a_glance">Your World At A Glance.</string>
    <string name="Next"></string>
    <string name="email_login">Login with Email</string>
    <string name="fb_login">Login with Facebook</string>
    <string name="tw_login">Login with Twitter</string>
    <string name="Login">Login</string>
    <string name="Email_Login">Email Login</string>
    <string name="Email_Address">Email Address</string>
    <string name="Password">Password</string>
    <string name="Dont_have_account">Don\'t have an account?</string>
    <string name="Sign_Up"><u>Sign Up</u></string>
    <string name="Create_Account">Create Account</string>
    <string name="First_Name">First Name</string>
    <string name="Last_Name">Last Name</string>
    <string name="Add_Photo">Add Photo</string>

    <!-- Global String Resource -->
    <string name="app_name">Vizo</string>
    <string name="done">done</string>
    <string name="back">back</string>
    <string name="next">next</string>

    <!-- String Resource for Last Glance View -->
    <string name="all_of_the">That\'s All of The</string>
    <string name="read_previous">Read Previous</string>
    <string name="looks_like_all_read">Looks Like You\'ve Read</string>
    <string name="change_category">Change Category</string>
    <string name="good_job">good job :)</string>
    <string name="or">or</string>

    <!-- String Resource for Glance Preview -->
    <string name="continue_hold">CONTINUE HOLDING TO VIEW GLANCE</string>
    <string name="release_to_cancel">release to cancel</string>

    <!-- String Resource for Glance Sharing View -->
    <string name="post_to_facebook">Post to Facebook</string>
    <string name="post_to_twitter">Post to Twitter</string>
    <string name="post_to_instagram">Post to Instagram</string>
    <string name="share_with_linkedin">Share with LinkedIn</string>
    <string name="text">Text</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>

    <!-- String Resource for Article Source View -->
    <string name="view_article_source">View Article Sources</string>
    <string name="save_image">Save Image</string>

    <!-- String Resource for Logo Settings -->
    <string name="no_account">No Account</string>
    <string name="Settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="Glanced">Glanced</string>
    <string name="Editions">Editions</string>

    <!-- String Resource for General Settings -->
    <string name="General">General</string>
    <string name="Show_Tips">Show Tips</string>
    <string name="Auto_Translate">Auto Translate</string>
    <string name="About">About</string>
    <string name="About_Vizo">About Vizo</string>
    <string name="Help_Feedback">Help &amp; Feedback</string>
    <string name="Rate_Us">Rate Us</string>

    <!-- String Resources for Preference Settings -->
    <string name="HOLD_DRAG">HOLD &amp; DRAG</string>
    <string name="Organize_Glance">Organize Glance</string>
    <string name="categories">categories</string>

    <!-- String Resource for Tutorials -->
    <string name="vizo_description">
        Vizo delivers today\'s top-trending\n
        global news headlines in brief,\n
        image-based summaries.</string>
    <string name="swipe_to_continue">Swipe to continue</string>
    <string name="tri_daily_update">Tri-daily update</string>
    <string name="tri_daily_update_description">
        Here at Vizo, we upload 15 stories three\n
        times a day - morning, afternoon\n
        and evening.</string>
    <string name="Glances">Glances</string>
    <string name="Glances_description">
        A glance is a new perspective on trending\n
        news stories consisting of a 500 characters\n
        synopsis &amp; a black and white image with\n
        accentuated focal points.</string>
    <string name="VizoU">VizoU</string>
    <string name="Tutorial_VizoU_Description">A revolutionary platform that allows anyone
        to become a journalist and publish their own articles. Take your own image,
        upload it and then share it with the world.</string>
    <string name="Glance_Preferences">Glance Preferences</string>
    <string name="Glance_Preferences_description">Tailor your news to your world. Customize\n
        your news feeds to ensure that you see the\n
        news you desire.</string>

    <!-- String Resource for About Page -->
    <string name="vizo_copyright">(c) Vizo, inc. 2015</string>
    <string name="vizo_version">Vizo 1.0</string>
    <string name="vizo_about">
        Vizo delivers today\'s top-trending global news headlines delivered in brief image-based
        summaries, three times a day We give you the latest and greatest news stories in a visually
        captivating and easily digestible format.</string>

    <!-- String Resource for Home Screen Walkthrough -->
    <string name="HOLD_VIZO">HOLD VIZO</string>
    <string name="to_view_your">to view your</string>
    <string name="Account">Account</string>
    <string name="and">and</string>
    <string name="adjust_your">adjust your</string>

    <string name="SWIPE_UP_OR_DOWN">SWIPE UP OR DOWN</string>
    <string name="Change_Glance_Categories">Change Glance Categories</string>

    <string name="TAP_THE_LIGHTNING_BOLT">TAP THE LIGHTNING BOLT</string>
    <string name="to_load">to load</string>
    <string name="New_Glances">New Glances</string>

    <!-- String Resources for State Of The Day -->
    <string name="State_Of_The_Day">State Of The Day</string>
    <string name="Help">Help</string>
    <string name="STAFF_PICKS">STAFF PICKS</string>
    <string name="TRENDING">TRENDING</string>

    <!-- String Resource for Full Glance Walkthrough -->
    <string name="SWIPE_DOWN">SWIPE DOWN</string>
    <string name="to_view">to view</string>
    <string name="Glance_Preview">Glance Preview</string>
    <string name="SWIPE_LEFT_OR_RIGHT">SWIPE LEFT OR RIGHT</string>
    <string name="to">to</string>
    <string name="Change_Glances">Change Glances</string>

    <!-- String Resources for Editions Page -->
    <string name="Choose_an_Edition">Choose an Edition</string>

    <!-- String Resources for Account Settings -->
    <string name="Account_Settings">Account Settings</string>
    <string name="Change_Password">Change Password</string>
    <string name="Old_Password">Old Password</string>
    <string name="New_Password">New Password</string>
    <string name="Confirm_Password">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="Accounts">Accounts</string>
    <string name="Manage_Accounts">Manage Accounts</string>
    <string name="Disconnect">Disconnect</string>
    <string name="Add_Account">Add Account</string>
    <string name="Logout">Logout</string>

    <!--String Resource for Vizo About-->
    <string name="Terms_of_Service">Terms of Service</string>
    <string name="Privacy_Policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="Credits">Credits</string>
    <string name="Agree">Agree</string>
    <string name="Decline">Decline</string>

    <!--String Resource for Vizo Help & Feedback-->
    <string name="FAQ">FAQ</string>
    <string name="Support">Support</string>
    <string name="Feedback">Feedback</string>
    <string name="Frequently_Asked_Questions">Frequently Asked Questions</string>

    <!-- String Resources for Glanced Page -->
    <string name="to_navigate_through">to navigate through</string>
    <string name="Glanced_Stories">Glanced Stories</string>
    <string name="TAP_THE_STAR">TAP THE STAR</string>
    <string name="to_only_view">to only view</string>
    <string name="Favorited_Glances">Favorited Glances</string>
    <string name="read_glance">read glance</string>
    <string name="Clear_All_History">Clear All History</string>
    <string name="no_glanced">No Glanced History</string>

    <!-- String Resources for VizoU Activity Page -->
    <string name="Activity">Activity</string>
    <string name="Create_Glance">Create Glance</string>
    <string name="Tap_to_add_a_photo">Tap to add a photo</string>
    <string name="Tap_to_change_photo">Tap to change photo</string>
    <string name="Preview">Preview</string>
    <string name="Delete_glance_confirmation">Are you sure you want to delete your glance?</string>
    <string name="Upload">Upload</string>
    <string name="Reshoot">Reshoot</string>
    <string name="Capture">Capture</string>
    <string name="Use">Use</string>
    <string name="Choose_a_Category">Choose a Category</string>
    <string name="Edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="Publish">Publish</string>
    <string name="Connect_Your_Facebook_Account">Connect Your Facebook Account</string>
    <string name="To_join_the_VizoU">To join the VizoU community and post glances</string>
    <string name="of">of</string>
    <string name="Character_minimum">Character Minimum</string>
    <string name="Characters_remaining">Characters remaining</string>
    <string name="Write_something_novel">Write something novel</string>

    <!-- String Resources for Date/Time stamp -->
    <string name="morning">Morning</string>
    <string name="afternoon">Afternoon</string>
    <string name="evening">Evening</string>

    <!-- String Resources for Sharing Content -->
    <string name="Want_to_read_more">Want to read more?
        Get the app today and experience Your World at a Glance. Next.™</string>
    <string name="Get_the_app_today">Get the app today</string>

    <!-- String Resource for Social Media authentication -->
    <string name="facebook_app_id">1567103316908435</string>

    <string name="privacy_policy_text">This Privacy Policy applies to Vizo Inc. (“Vizo,” “we,” or “us”), the Vizo application (including all related documentation, the “Application”), the Vizo website (located at http://www.vizonews.com) (the “Website”), any other services provided through the Application or Website (collectively with the Application and Website, the “Service”), and you when you use the Service. It explains the types of information Vizo may collect—or that you may provide—when you use the Service; how the information will be used; with whom we share your information; and how you can control the collection, use, sharing, update, and deletion of your information. This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect in the Application, on the Website, in connection with the Service, in e-mail, and other electronic communications sent through or in connection with the Service. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information we collect by other means (including offline) or from other sources.  Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. By accessing or using the Website, Application, or Service, you consent to the collection, use, processing, and sharing of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, do not access or use the Website, Application, or Service. You may access the Service from a mobile device or computer, including through a third party social networking site or service such as Facebook.com (a “Social Networking Service”). If you access the Service through a Social Networking Service, you may also be required to accept that Social Networking Service’s terms of use agreement and privacy policy.  Changes to this Privacy Policy.    PLEASE NOTE THAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY MAY CHANGE FROM TIME TO TIME. We will notify you of material changes to this Privacy Policy by posting the applicable changes on the Service at least thirty (30) days prior to the effective date of the changes. Except as otherwise stated, amendments and changes will become effective thirty (30) days following their initial posting. In addition, for users who have registered to use the Application and provided their email address to us, we will send notice of any material changes to this Privacy Policy by email, and so it is important that you keep your email address with us current. If you do not agree to any of the terms of this Privacy Policy or any future Privacy Policy provided by Vizo, do not use, access, or continue to access the Service.  If you continue using the Service after the new terms take effect, you will be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.   Children under the Age of 13. Vizo does not permit children under the age of thirteen (13) to use the Service, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have collected or received personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information. Information We Collect. Information Received from Social Networking Services.  When you access the Service through a Social Networking Service, information associated with your account or profile on that Social Networking Service may be provided to us by the applicable Social Networking Service. Depending on your privacy settings for the applicable Social Networking Service, this information may include your name; gender; birthday; profile picture; contacts; device information; profile information such as biography, education, occupation, and employer; data made available by you and your friends; location; time zone; and the location of the devices you use to access the Service. You should check the privacy policy, and your privacy settings and controls, for the applicable Social Networking Service to learn more about how you can control the information collected and shared by the Social Networking Service with us. Information Received from Mobile Devices or Personal Computers.  When you access the Service through a mobile device we may receive and collect information such as the type and identification of that mobile device, its location, telephone number, and mobile network information. The Application also may access metadata and other information associated with other files stored on your device. This may include, for example, photographs, audio and video clips, personal contacts, and address book information. We may also use this information to track your use of the Service and allow you to invite, or be invited by, other users to use the Application. Information You Provide to Us Directly.  By accessing or using the Service, we will directly collect information about you as follows: User Account and Profile.  If you access the Service through a means other than a Social Networking Service, you may be required to provide information such as your email address, name, postal address, and telephone number in order to create an account within the Service. We may also allow you to create a user profile which will be visible to other users of the Service. Such profile information may include your name and/or user name, profile picture, biographical information, information about your use of the Service, and links to profiles of you on Social Networking Services.   Correspondence and User Content.  If you correspond with us by email, text, or other messaging (including for support purposes), we may retain records and copies of your messages, your email address, telephone number, and our responses. We may also retain any messages you send through the Service either to us or other users. In addition, any content, comments, questions, and other information that you upload, publish, display, link to, or otherwise make available on or through the public areas of the Service (“User Content”) is considered public, may be accessed by us and other users, may be indexed by search engines or other means, and we may store such information. User Activity.  When you use the Service, we may collect information about your use of the Service including but not limited to your usage, patterns of use, traffic data, location data, logs, searches resources accessed, transactions carried out through the Service, and interactions with other users.  Information Automatically Collected Through the Service. Cookies.  When you use the Service from a computer, we may send one or more small files called “cookies” to your computer that uniquely identify your browser and let us help you log in faster, track, and enhance your navigation through the Service. We may also use cookies to collect information about how you use the Service. Third parties that deliver advertisements to users of the Service may also use cookies, and their use of cookies is governed by their own policies and practices. You can set your web browser to refuse certain types of cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. If you set your browser to limit or remove cookies, some features of the Service may be unavailable or may not function properly. We may also engage in behavioral tracking by collecting information about your activities over time and across third-party websites, applications, or other online services.  Log Files.  Log file information is automatically reported by your browser or Social Networking Service each time you access the Service from your computer. We may also use log files and server logs to collect information about your use of the Service, which provides a more personal and richer user experience. These log files and server logs may include information such as your web request, IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages and URLs, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, and pages viewed. Clear GIFs or Web Beacons:  When you use the Service from your computer, and email or message us, we may employ clear GIFs (also known as web beacons) which are also small files used to track the online usage patterns of our users so that we may better understand how people use the Service, and improve the user experience. We do not share usage information with third parties, except in the form of aggregate data that does not specifically identify individual users and except as necessary to prevent illegal activities and enforce our Terms of Use Agreement.  Third Parties’ Use of Cookies and Web Beacons:  The Service may include third-party advertising, links to other websites, and other content from third-party businesses. These third-parties may use cookies and web beacons to track the actions of users online over time and across different websites or platforms to deliver targeted electronic advertisements to an individual user. For information about how tracking works for online advertising purposes you can visit http://www.aboutads.info/choices.    Vizo does not have access to or control over web beacons or cookies that third party websites may use. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these third-party websites.  You are encouraged to review the privacy policies of the different websites you visit. In addition, some third-party advertising companies may provide a mechanism to opt-out of their technology.  For more information about the opt-out process, you may visit the Network Advertising Initiative website, available at: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.  In addition, your browser may allow you to adjust your browser settings so that “do not track” requests are sent to the websites that you visit. However, we will not disable tracking technology that may be active on the Service in response to any “do not track” requests that we receive from your browser.  How We Use Your Information. General.  We use the information that you provide and we collect to operate, maintain, provide, and improve the features and functionality of the Service and to create a personalized and rich user experience. In addition, we may use your information for other purposes including, but not limited to: (a) create your Service account and allow use of the Service; (b) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your next visit or use of the Service; (c) update your user profile; (d) customize and personalize the user experience; (e) monitor the effectiveness of our Service; (f) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of users, traffic, and demographic patterns; (g) notify you of Service updates or new products or promotional offers; (h) solicit feedback from you about how we can improve the Service; (i) respond to your inquiries; (j) provide technical support and diagnose or fix technology problems reported by our users or engineers that are associated with certain IP addresses; (k) help you efficiently access your information after you sign in; (l) track User Content and users to the extent necessary to prevent illegal activities, enforce our Terms of Use Agreement, and comply with applicable law; and (m) deliver targeted advertisements.  Use of Your Email Address.  By providing us with your email address, including by adding the Application on a Social Networking Service, you consent to our using the email address to send you Service-related notices in lieu of communication by postal mail, except as required by applicable law. You also agree that we may send you notifications of activity on the Service to the email address you give us, in accordance with your privacy settings. We may use your email address to send you other messages, such as newsletters, new features or applications, changes to features of the Service, or special offers. If you do not want to receive email messages from us, you may opt-out by sending an email with “opt-out” in the subject line to help@vizonews.com or by following the unsubscribe link in the applicable email. Opting out may prevent you from receiving email messages regarding updates, improvements, or other offers. You may not opt-out of Service-related e-mails. How We Share Your Information. Our Service Providers.  We may share your personal information with our third party providers for the purpose of providing the Service to you. When we do this, these third parties’ use of your information will be subject to this Privacy Policy.  Aggregate Information.  We may share, sell, resell, or otherwise monetize information that does not identify you personally (such as anonymous aggregated data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, and etc.) with third parties. We note that, while this information will not identify you personally, in some instances these third parties may be able to combine this information with other data they have about you, or that they receive from third parties, in a manner that allows them to identify you personally.  Response to Subpoenas or Court Orders or to Protect Rights and to Comply with Our Policies.  Except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, we will not disclose personal information to any third party unless required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that this action is necessary to (a) conform to the law, comply with legal process served on us or our affiliates, or investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities; (b) enforce our Terms of Use; (c) take precautions against liability; (d) investigate and defend ourselves against third-party claims or allegations; (e) assist government enforcement agencies; (f) protect the security or integrity of the Service; or (g) exercise or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of us, our users or others. Business Transfers; Bankruptcy.  In the event of a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, or other sale of all or a portion of our assets, any user information owned or controlled by us may be one of the assets transferred to third parties. We reserve the right, as part of this type of transaction, to transfer or assign your information and other information we have collected from users of the Service to third parties. Other than to the extent ordered by a bankruptcy or other court, the use and disclosure of all transferred user information will be subject to this Privacy Policy. However, any information you submit or that is collected after this type of transfer may be subject to a new privacy policy adopted by the successor entity. Marketing Partners.  We may occasionally provide your information to marketing partners or other third parties that may then contact you with marketing and other information about products, services, or publications in which we believe you may have an interest. You can elect to opt-out of having your information shared with these third parties either by (a) during the registration process, un-checking the box granting us permission to share your information with third parties for their own marketing purposes, (b) adjusting the settings in your user account, or (c) contacting us at help@vizonews.com. We will stop sharing your information with third parties for their own marketing purposes within a reasonable time period following our receipt of your election to opt-out.  However, if we have shared your information with a third party prior to this time, that third party will continue to have your information and may continue to send marketing communications to you. In this case, if you no longer want to receive marketing communications from the applicable third party, you will need to notify the applicable third party directly. Our Affiliates.  We may share some or all of your information with our parent company, subsidiaries, corporate affiliates, joint venturers, or other companies under common control with us. We will require these entities to comply with the terms of this Privacy Policy with regard to their use of your information.   How We Protect Your Information. We use commercially reasonable physical and technical safeguards to preserve the security of your personal information and implement your privacy settings. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that this information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. We cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Your privacy settings may also be affected by changes to the functionality of Social Networking Services through which you access the Service. We are not responsible for the functionality or security measures employed by any third party. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information, and for controlling access to your email communications from us, at all times. Your Choices About Your Information. You may decline to submit personal information to the Service, in which case we may not be able to provide certain services to you.  You can manage or control the information we receive from a Social Networking Service by following the instructions provided by that Social Networking Service.  You may update or correct your account information and email preferences at any time within the Application.  You may change your privacy settings within the Service through the features provided in applicable Social Networking Service.  In addition, if you are a California resident under the age of 18 and are a registered user of the Service, you may request that we remove content or information about you that you posted on the Service by (a) submitting a request in writing to help@vizonews.com and (b) clearly identifying the content or information you wish to have removed and providing sufficient information to allow us to locate the content or information to be removed. However, please note that we are not required to erase or otherwise eliminate content or information if (i) other state or federal laws require us or a third party to maintain the content or information; (ii) the content or information was posted, stored, or republished by another user; (iii) the content or information is anonymized so that you cannot be individually identified; (iv) you do not follow the instructions posted in this Privacy Policy on how to request removal of your content or information; or (v) you have received compensation or other consideration for providing the content. Further, nothing in this provision shall be construed to limit the authority of a law enforcement agency to obtain the applicable content or information. Links to Other Websites. We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from the Service. If you visit these websites or provide any information directly to parties other than us, different policies may apply to the collection and use of your information. We encourage you to investigate and ask questions before accessing third party websites or disclosing information to third parties.  Use of Information Outside Your Country of Residence. At this time, the Service is provided from the United States and is intended for users located in the United States. If you are located outside of the United States and you choose to use the Service or provide your information to us, your information may be transferred to, processed and maintained on servers or databases located in the United States.  Your use of the Service represents your consent and agreement to these practices. If you do not want your information transferred to or processed or maintained in the United States, you should not use the Service. Contact Information. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, our practice, or your dealings with the Service, please contact us at help@vizonews.com.</string>
    <string name="tos_text"> Vizo Inc. Terms of Use Agreement Welcome to the online services operated by Vizo Inc. (the “Company,” “we,” or “us”). This Terms of Use Agreement (“Agreement”) constitutes a binding agreement between you (“End User” or “you”) and the Company (you and Company may be referred to in this Agreement collectively as the “Parties”). This Agreement governs your use of any mobile applications provided by us including, without limitation, the Vizo application (including all related documentation, the “Application”); the Vizo website (located at http://www.vizonews.com) (the “Website”); and any other services provided through the Application or Website (collectively with the Application and Website, the “Service”). The Application is licensed, not sold, to you. BY (A) VISITING OR USING THE WEBSITE; (B) ACCESSING, ACTIVATING, OR USING THE SERVICE OR APPLICATION; OR (C) CREATING AN ACCOUNT (EITHER DIRECTLY THROUGH THE SERVICE OR THROUGH A THIRD PARTY SOCIAL NETWORKING SERVICE, SUCH AS FACEBOOK, INC. (A “SOCIAL NETWORKING SERVICE”)), YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THIS AGREEMENT If you access the Service through a third party website, Social Networking Service, or mobile applications provider the applicable third party website, Social Networking Service or mobile applications provider may have additional terms and conditions that are applicable to your use of the  applicable website, Social Networking Service or mobile application and you must also comply with these terms and conditions, as applicable. Notice Regarding Dispute Resolution: This Agreement contains provisions that govern how claims you and we may have against each other are resolved (see Section 21 below), including an agreement and obligation to arbitrate disputes, which will, subject to limited exceptions, require you to submit claims you have against us to binding arbitration, unless you opt-out in accordance with Section 21. Unless you opt-out of arbitration: (a) you will only be permitted to pursue claims against us on an individual basis, not as part of any class or representative action or proceeding and (b) you will only be permitted to seek relief (including monetary, injunctive, and declaratory relief) on an individual basis. Affirmative Representations Regarding Your Use of the Service:   WHEN YOU USE THE SERVICE, YOU REPRESENT AND WARRANT TO THE COMPANY THAT (A) YOU HAVE READ AND UNDERSTAND THIS AGREEMENT; (B) YOU ARE AT LEAST 13 YEARS OF AGE; AND (C) YOU ARE OF SUFFICIENT LEGAL AGE OR OTHERWISE HAVE LEGAL CAPACITY TO LEGALLY ENTER INTO THIS AGREEMENT.  Privacy Policy.   In connection with your use of the Service, please review our Privacy Policy, located at http://www.vizonews.com/privacy, to understand how we use information we collect from you when you access, visit, or use the Service. The Privacy Policy is part of and is governed by this Agreement and by agreeing to the terms of this Agreement, you agree to be bound by the terms of the Privacy Policy and agree that we may use information collected from you in accordance with its terms.   Account. In order to participate in or receive certain portions of the Service (including, but not limited to, the Application), you will be required to create an account with the Company (“Account”) and you may also be required to maintain an account with the Social Networking Service through which you access the Service or with the applications provider for your supported Mobile Device. Once you create an Account, your Account will allow you to access the Application. You may control certain aspects of how you interact with the Service by changing your settings in the Application and/or the Social Networking Site through which you access the Service. The Application settings permit you to choose you preferences with regard to the layout of content displayed to you within the Application. When accessing the Service through a Social Networking Service, your ability to adjust the settings that control these settings is solely within the control of the Social Networking Service you use. Your Account is for your individual, personal, and non-commercial use only, and you may not authorize others to use your Account for any purpose. By creating your Account, you certify that all information you provide is complete and accurate. You agree to update your information when required or requested, and you further agree not to use another persons account without permission. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of, and restricting access to, your Account and the associated password, and you agree to accept sole responsibility for all activities that occur under your Account or password. You agree to notify us immediately at help@vizonews.com of any breach of security or unauthorized use of your Account or any violation of this Agreement by others of which you are aware. Service Requirements. In order to access or participate in the Service, you will need telecommunications access to a mobile phone, tablet, or personal computer mobile device owned or otherwise controlled by you, connected to the internet, and compatible with the Service (each a “Device”). You will also be responsible, at your expense, for all telecommunications access and telephone service required to access or participate in the Service and all related third-party service fees (including ISP charges). Certain messaging, service, and other fees and charges may be applied by your carrier. Please check with your carrier to ensure that you are aware of any applicable fees and charges relating to your particular service plan. The Company is not responsible for any expenses incurred by you while accessing or using the Service. Company Proprietary Rights; License Grant. Reservation of Rights. You acknowledge and agree that the Service is provided under license and is not sold to you. You do not acquire any ownership interest in the Service under this Agreement or any other rights other than to use the Service in accordance with the license granted and subject to all terms, conditions, and restrictions under this Agreement. The Company and its licensors and service providers reserve and retain exclusive ownership of—and all right, title, and interest in and to—the Service and all content and materials provided in connection with the Service (other than Personal Content, as described below), and all related intellectual property rights, subject only to the limited license granted to you in Section 5.2.  Grant of License. Subject to your full compliance with this Agreement and the Companys Privacy Policy (located at http://www.vizonews.com/privacy), we hereby grant you a limited, non-exclusive, revocable, personal, and non-transferable license to: Access and use the Application for your personal, non-commercial use on any Device; and Access, download, and use the Service made available in or otherwise accessible through the Application on a Device, strictly in accordance with this Agreement. License Restrictions; Prohibited Content. You agree that you will not in connection with your use of the Service: Decompile, reverse engineer, disassemble, decode, decompile, attempt to access the source code, or sublicense the Service, or any portion of the Service; Modify, translate, adapt, or create improvements or derivative works of the Application; Alter, obscure, remove, or delete any trademarks or any trademark, copyright, patent, or other intellectual property or proprietary rights notices from the Service; Rent, lease, lend, sell, sublicense, assign, distribute, publish, transfer, or otherwise make available the Application or any features or functionality of the Application, to any third party for any reason, including by making the Application available on a network where it is capable of being accessed by more than one device at any time; Employ misleading email addresses or mobile numbers or falsify information in any part of any communication related to the Service; Engage in any activity which may compromise the stability or availability of the Service or use the Service to compromise the availability or stability of any third party site or service; Use automated means, including spiders, robots, crawlers, or the like to download data from the Service or any related server or database; Circumvent any security measures or any payment collection methods employed on or through the Service, or access or use the Service after the Company terminates or suspends your Account, this Agreement, or your access; By-pass the measures used to prevent or restrict access to the Service, including but not limited to, features that prevent or restrict use or copying of any content or enforce limitations on use of the Service or the Services content; Abuse or harass any other user, member or person; Collect or store personally identifying information about other users for commercial or unlawful purposes; Impersonate any person or entity; Employ misleading email addresses or mobile numbers or falsify information in any part of any communication related to the Service or Website; Use the Service for any unsolicited advertising or promotions; Upload post, email, otherwise transmit or post links to any content or material, or create an Account using any member or user name or email address in a manner that is unlawful; harmful; threatening; abusive; harassing; tortious; defamatory; vulgar; obscene; pornographic; libelous; invasive of privacy or publicity rights; hateful; or racially, sexually, ethnically, or otherwise objectionable; Upload, post, email, otherwise transmit or post links to any content or material that infringes any patent, trademark, service mark, trade secret, copyright, or other proprietary rights of any person or that contributes to, induces, or facilitates this type of infringement; Upload, post, email, otherwise transmit, or post links to any content or material that contains software viruses; worms; Trojan horses; time bombs; trap doors; any other computer code, files, or programs; or repetitive requests for information designed to interrupt, destroy, or limit the functionality of any computer software or hardware or telecommunications equipment or to diminish the quality of, interfere with the performance of, or impair the functionality of the Service or any third party software, site, equipment, or service; or Upload, post, email, otherwise transmit or post links to any content or material that violates any applicable law, statute, ordinance, or regulation, or which we deem improper in our sole discretion. User Content. Submission of User Content. Some areas of the Service may allow you and other users to post content, comments, questions, and other information (“User Content”). You acknowledge and agree that your communications with other users via chats, conferences, bulletin boards, blogs, posts, and any other publicly accessible avenues of communication through the Service are public and not private communications. Therefore, we strongly encourage you to use caution before disclosing any personal information about yourself in your public communications. You are solely responsible for the User Content that you upload, publish, display, link to, or otherwise make available (hereinafter, “post”) on or through the Service. We reserve the right to refuse to transmit or post (and to disclose, block, or remove) any content or materials—including but not limited to, User Content, in whole or in part—that we in our discretion deem to violate this Agreement, our policies and procedures, or that we otherwise deem harmful to persons using the Service, regardless of whether the material or its dissemination is unlawful. In addition, we may also take preventative steps including, but not limited to, limiting or filtering the number of posts sent or received by a user. Your Representations and Warranties about Your User Content. By posting User Content on or through the Service, you represent and warrant that: None of us, our customers, licensees, or business partners will be required to make any payments with respect to your User Content, including but not limited to, payments to you, your agents, your affiliates, your licensors, all third parties, or any persons who contributed to or appear in your User Content; You have full right, power, and authority to post your User Content and have secured all third-party consents, licenses, and permissions necessary to post your User Content and grant to us the rights and licenses described below; and Your User Content (A) is not defamatory; (B) does not infringe upon, misappropriate, or violate the rights of any third party including, but not limited to, any intellectual property rights, rights of publicity, or any other privacy or proprietary rights; and (C) does not violate any law, rule, regulation, or ordinance. Rights in User Content. As between you and the Company, you retain all your ownership rights in your User Content. However, by uploading, making available or submitting User Content, you grant us and our business partners and affiliates a royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable, world-wide, assignable, and transferable right and license to quote, re-post, use, copy, reproduce, modify, create derivative works of, incorporate into other works, distribute, transmit, broadcast, communicate, publicly display, publicly perform, and otherwise exploit your User Content in any form or media now known or hereafter created, anywhere, and without any notice or compensation to you of any kind. You hereby grant us all consents, rights, and clearances to enable us to use your User Content for these purposes. Without limiting the foregoing, we may: Host your User Content on our servers and those of our third party service providers that we may engage to host the Service and display your User Content, in whole or in part, alone or in compilation with content provided by third parties, to other users of the Service or Website; Re-encode your User Content as needed to be compatible with different mobile devices; Edit your User Content to ensure that it complies with our policies and guidelines; and Use any trademarks, service marks, or trade names incorporated into your User Content and the likeness of any individual whose performance or image is contained in your User Content.  Copyright Complaints; DMCA Notification.  We may, in our sole discretion, remove any User Content that appears to infringe on the intellectual property rights of others. We may, in our sole discretion, terminate access to the Service by users who infringe or appear to infringe on the intellectual property rights of others. Your Interactions with Other Users. YOU ARE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR YOUR INTERACTIONS WITH OTHER USERS OF THE SERVICE. YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT WE RESERVE THE RIGHT, BUT HAVE NO OBLIGATION, TO SCREEN OUR USERS, INQUIRE INTO THE BACKGROUNDS OF OUR USERS, AND ATTEMPT TO VERIFY THE STATEMENTS OF OUR USERS. PLEASE ALSO USE CAUTION, COMMON SENSE, AND SAFETY WHEN USING THE SERVICE TO INTERACT WITH OTHER USERS.   WE RESERVE THE RIGHT, BUT HAVE NO OBLIGATION, TO MONITOR DISPUTES BETWEEN YOU AND OTHER USERS OR TO TERMINATE OR BLOCK YOU AND OTHER USERS FOR VIOLATIONS OF THIS AGREEMENT. Release. In the event that you have a dispute with one or more other users, you hereby release us, our parent, subsidiaries, and affiliated entities and ours and their shareholders, directors, officers, employees, agents, successors, and assigns from any and all claims, demands, damages (actual and consequential), losses, and liabilities of every kind or nature, known and unknown, suspected and unsuspected, disclosed and undisclosed, arising out of or in any way related to any dispute. If you are a California resident, you waive California Civil Code Section 1542, which says: “A general release does not extend to claims which the creditor does not know or suspect to exist in his favor at the time of executing the release, which, if known by him must have materially affected his settlement with the debtor.” Advertising and Computational Resources. As consideration for the license and rights granted to you under this Agreement, you agree that (A) the Company and its business partners have the right to provide ads, promotions, offers, and other information to you by email or other means of communication; and (B) we may allow the Service to utilize the processor, bandwidth, and storage hardware on your Devices for the purposes of facilitating (i) the communication and transmission of content and other data or features to you and other users of the Service; and (ii) the operation of the network(s) on which the Service runs. You may opt out of receiving promotional messages from the Company at any time by pressing the “unsubscribe” link in any of the emails containing the promotional messages from the Company. Third Party Content.  The Application may display, include, or make available third-party content (including data, information, applications, and other products, services, or materials) or provide links to third-party websites or services, including through third-party advertising (“Third Party Materials”). You acknowledge and agree that the Company has no control over and is not responsible for Third Party Materials, including their accuracy, completeness, timeliness, validity, copyright compliance, use of personal information, legality, decency, quality, or any other aspect thereof. The Company does not assume and will not have any liability or responsibility to you or any other person or entity for any Third Party Materials. Third Party Materials, and links to Third Party Materials, are provided solely as a convenience to End Users; your access and use of them is entirely at your own risk and subject to the terms and conditions of use provided by the applicable third party. Application Updates.  The Company may from time to time and in its sole discretion develop and provide Service updates, which may include upgrades, bug fixes, patches, other error corrections, and new features (collectively, including related documentation, “Updates”). Updates may also modify or delete in their entirety certain features and functionality. You agree that the Company has no obligation to provide any Updates or to continue to provide or enable any particular features or functionality. Based on your Device settings, when your Device is connected to the internet, either (A) the Application will automatically download and install all available Updates, or (B) you may receive notice of or be prompted to download and install available Updates. You will promptly download and install all Updates and acknowledge and agree that the Service or portions thereof may not properly operate if you fail to do so. You further agree that all Updates will become part of the Service and subject to all terms and conditions of this Agreement. Maintenance requirements or technical difficulties may result in temporary interruptions of the Service from time to time. The Company reserves the right at any time and from time to time to modify or discontinue, temporarily or permanently, functions and features of the Service with or without notice.  The Company will not be liable to you or to any third party for any of the direct or indirect consequences of any modification, malfunction, suspension, discontinuance of, or interruption to the Service.   Agreement Updates. We may modify this Agreement from time to time. We will notify you of material changes to this Agreement by posting the applicable changes on the Service at least thirty (30) days prior to the effective date of the changes. Except as otherwise stated, amendments and changes will become effective thirty (30) days following their initial posting. Please return to this page periodically to ensure familiarity with the most current version of this Agreement. In addition, for users who have registered to use the Application and provided their email address to us, we will send notice of any material changes to this Agreement by email, and so it is important that you keep your email address with us current. Your continued access or use of the Service following changes to this Agreement will constitute acceptance of the amendments and changes. If you do not agree to any of the terms of this Agreement or any future Terms of Use Agreement provided by the Company, do not use, access, or continue to access the Service. If you continue using the Service after the new terms take effect, you will be bound by the modified Terms of Use Agreement.  Email Notices. You agree that the Company will use your email address to send you messages related to the Service, in lieu of communication by postal mail or other methods, except where the Company is expressly required by applicable law to provide other notice. The Company may also use your email address to send you other messages, such as changes to features of the Service, new applications, and special offers. If you do not want to receive these messages, you may opt out by using the unsubscribe option in the applicable email. Opting out may prevent you from receiving email messages regarding updates, improvements, or offers.  Geographic Restrictions. The Service is based in the United States and provided for access and use only by persons located in the United States. You acknowledge that you may not be able to access all or some of the Service outside of the United States and that access thereto may not be legal by certain persons or in certain countries. If you access the Service from outside the United States, you are responsible for compliance with local laws. Termination. You may terminate this Agreement by cancelling your Account according to the procedures provided by the Application or the Website. If you cancel your account you will no longer be able to access your account or use the Service as a registered user. The Company reserves the right without liability to terminate or restrict this Agreement, your Account, or your access to or use of the Application or Service with or without notice for any reason. In particular, this Agreement will immediately and automatically terminate without notice if you violate any of its terms and conditions. You agree that the Company will not be liable to you or any third-party for any interference with or termination of your access to the Application or Service. The Company will make all decisions regarding the termination of this Agreement or your Account in its sole discretion. The Company is not required to disclose the reason for termination of this Agreement or your Account.  Upon termination all rights granted to you under this Agreement will terminate; you will cease all use of the Application and delete the Application from all Devices. Sections 18, 20, 21, 22, and 23 will survive termination of this Agreement. Disclaimer of Warranties. THE COMPANY PROVIDES THE APPLICATION TO END USER “AS IS” AND WITH ALL FAULTS AND DEFECTS WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED UNDER APPLICABLE LAW, THE COMPANY—ON ITS OWN BEHALF AND ON BEHALF OF ITS AFFILIATES AND ITS AND THEIR RESPECTIVE LICENSORS AND SERVICE PROVIDERS—EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, WHETHER EXPRESS, IMPLIED, STATUTORY, OR OTHERWISE WITH RESPECT TO THE APPLICATION. THIS DISCLAIMER INCLUDES ALL IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE, AND NON-INFRINGEMENT WHETHER THEY MAY ARISE OUT OF A COURSE OF DEALING, COURSE OF PERFORMANCE, USAGE, OR TRADE PRACTICE. WITHOUT LIMITATION TO THE FOREGOING, THE COMPANY PROVIDES NO WARRANTY OR UNDERTAKING AND MAKES NO REPRESENTATION OF ANY KIND THAT THE APPLICATION WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS; ACHIEVE ANY INTENDED RESULTS; BE COMPATIBLE OR WORK WITH ANY OTHER SOFTWARE, APPLICATIONS, SYSTEMS, OR SERVICES; OPERATE WITHOUT INTERRUPTION; MEET ANY PERFORMANCE OR RELIABILITY STANDARDS; BE ERROR FREE; OR THAT ANY ERRORS OR DEFECTS CAN OR WILL BE CORRECTED. TO THE EXTENT APPLICABLE LAWS PROHIBIT TERMS OF USE FROM DISCLAIMING ANY IMPLIED WARRANTY, THE APPLICABLE IMPLIED WARRANTY WILL BE LIMITED TO THE MINIMUM WARRANTY AND WARRANTY PERIOD REQUIRED BY LAW. Limitation of Liability. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, IN NO EVENT WILL THE COMPANY OR ITS AFFILIATES, OR ANY OF ITS OR THEIR RESPECTIVE LICENSORS OR SERVICE PROVIDERS, HAVE ANY LIABILITY ARISING FROM OR RELATED TO YOUR USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THE APPLICATION OR THE CONTENT AND SERVICES FOR: (A) PERSONAL INJURY, PROPERTY DAMAGE, LOST PROFITS, COST OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES, LOSS OF DATA, LOSS OF GOODWILL, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, COMPUTER FAILURE OR MALFUNCTION, OR ANY OTHER CONSEQUENTIAL, INCIDENTAL, INDIRECT, EXEMPLARY, SPECIAL, OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES; OR (B) DIRECT DAMAGES IN AMOUNTS THAT IN THE AGGREGATE EXCEED THE AMOUNT ACTUALLY PAID BY YOU FOR THE APPLICATION. THESE LIMITATIONS WILL APPLY WHETHER ANY DAMAGES ARISE OUT OF BREACH OF CONTRACT, TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE), OR OTHERWISE AND REGARDLESS OF WHETHER ANY DAMAGES WERE FORESEEABLE OR THE COMPANY WAS ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF ANY DAMAGES.  Force Majeure. The Company will not be liable for any delay or failure in performance of the Service by an event beyond the Companys control, without its fault or negligence, and that by its nature could not have been foreseen by the Company or—if it could have been foreseen—was unavoidable. Indemnification. You agree to indemnify, defend, and hold harmless the Company and its officers, directors, employees, agents, affiliates, successors, and assigns from and against any and all losses, damages, liabilities, deficiencies, claims, actions, judgments, settlements, interest, awards, penalties, fines, costs, or expenses of whatever kind (including attorneys fees) arising from or relating to your use or misuse of the Service or your breach of this Agreement. Arbitration Agreement and Waiver of Class Remedies. Arbitration.  All claims arising out of or relating to this Agreement and the Service will be finally settled by binding arbitration administered by the American Arbitration Association (“AAA”) in accordance with the provisions of the Consumer Arbitration Rules of the AAA, excluding any rules or procedures governing or permitting class actions. The arbitrator—and not any federal, state, or local court or agency—will have exclusive authority to resolve all disputes arising out of or relating to this Agreement. The arbitrator will be empowered to grant whatever relief would be available in a court under law or in equity. The arbitrators award will be binding on the Parties and may be entered as a judgment in any court of competent jurisdiction. The interpretation and enforcement of these Terms of Service shall be subject to the Federal Arbitration Act. THE AAAS RULES GOVERNING THE ARBITRATION MAY BE ACCESSED AT WWW.ADR.ORG OR BY CALLING THE AAA AT 1.800.778.7879. TO THE EXTENT THE FILING FEE FOR THE ARBITRATION EXCEEDS THE COST OF FILING A LAWSUIT, WE WILL PAY THE ADDITIONAL COST. IF WE ARE REQUIRED TO PAY THE ADDITIONAL COST OF THE FILING FEES, YOU SHOULD SUBMIT A REQUEST FOR PAYMENT OF FEES TO AAA ALONG WITH YOUR FORM FOR INITIATING THE ARBITRATION, AND WE WILL MAKE ARRANGEMENTS TO PAY ALL NECESSARY FEES DIRECTLY TO AAA. THE ARBITRATION RULES ALSO PERMIT YOU TO RECOVER ATTORNEYS FEES IN CERTAIN CIRCUMSTANCES.  THE PARTIES UNDERSTAND THAT, ABSENT THIS MANDATORY PROVISION, THEY WOULD HAVE THE RIGHT TO SUE IN COURT AND HAVE A JURY TRIAL. THEY FURTHER UNDERSTAND THAT, IN SOME INSTANCES, THE COSTS OF ARBITRATION COULD EXCEED THE COSTS OF LITIGATION AND THE RIGHT TO DISCOVERY MAY BE MORE LIMITED IN ARBITRATION THAN IN COURT. Class Action Waiver. The Parties further agree that any arbitration will be conducted in their individual capacities only and not as a class action or other representative action, and the Parties expressly waive their right to file a class action or seek relief on a class basis. If any court or arbitrator determines that the class action waiver set forth in this section is void or unenforceable for any reason or that an arbitration can proceed on a class basis, then the arbitration provision set forth above will be deemed null and void in its entirety and the Parties will be deemed to have not agreed to arbitrate disputes. Small Claims Exception. Notwithstanding the Parties decision to resolve all disputes through arbitration, either party may also seek relief in a small claims court for disputes or claims within the scope of that courts jurisdiction. Thirty Day Right to Opt Out. You have the right to opt-out and not be bound by the arbitration and class action waiver provisions set forth in this section by sending written notice of your decision to opt-out to the following address: ____________________, Attention: ________. The notice must be sent within thirty (30) days of registering to use the Service, otherwise you will be bound to arbitrate disputes in accordance with the terms set forth above. If you opt-out of these arbitration provisions, then the Company also will not be bound by them. In addition, if you elect to opt-out of these arbitration provisions, then the Company may terminate your use of the Service. Exclusive Venue for Litigation. To the extent that the arbitration provisions set forth in Section 21.1 do not apply, the parties agree that any litigation between them will be filed exclusively in state or federal courts located in State of New York (except for small claims court actions which may be brought in the county where you reside). The parties expressly consent to exclusive jurisdiction in the State of New York for any litigation other than small claims court actions. Applicable Law. You agree that federal laws and the laws of the State of New York, without regard to principles of conflict of laws, will govern these Terms of Use and any claim or dispute that has arisen or may arise between you and the Company. Claim Limitation. ANY CAUSE OF ACTION OR CLAIM YOU MAY HAVE ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO THIS AGREEMENT OR THE SERVICE MUST BE COMMENCED WITHIN ONE (1) YEAR AFTER THE CAUSE OF ACTION ACCRUES, OTHERWISE THAT CAUSE OF ACTION OR CLAIM IS PERMANENTLY BARRED. Severability.  If any provision of this Agreement is illegal or unenforceable under applicable law, the remainder of the provision will be amended to achieve as closely as possible the effect of the original term and all other provisions of this Agreement will continue in full force and effect. Waiver. No delay or failure to take action under this Agreement will constitute any waiver by the Company of any provision of this Agreement. Assignment This Agreement is personal to you and may not be transferred, assigned, or delegated by you to any other person or entity. Any attempt by you to assign, transfer, or delegate this Agreement will be null and void. Entire Agreement. This Agreement and the Companys Privacy Policy constitute the complete and exclusive agreement between the Company and you with respect to their subject matter and they supersede all prior oral or written understandings, communications, or agreements. There are no third party beneficiaries of this Agreement or the Companys Privacy Policy.</string>
</resources>
